Integration.
Protecting wild animals. A.
Daniel is reading two articles about wild animals.
Read with him and answer the questions below.
We live in the Arctic.
We are the biggest meat-eaters on land, and we often have to travel a long way to find food.
The Earth is becoming warmer, and the Arctic ice is melting.
This makes it more difficult for us to survive.
Today, there are about 22,000 to 31,000 of us on Earth, and our number may still drop.
We are the largest animals on the planet, the ocean is our home, and we can live up to 90 years.
In the past, humans hunted us, and there were very few of us left.
Now, it is against the law to hunt us, but we are still at risk.
Big ships often hit and hurt us.
What's more, the ocean water is getting warmer, and we may not have enough food to eat in the future.
It is harder for us to live long and healthy lives than before.